Hey, what's up?
Show me something that I can
buy for bottom drawers.
- Is your daughter getting married?
- Yeah.
- Her father-in-law is a doctor.
- She's got a rich husband.
If you don't like this, I can show you
some dishes that are from France.
Her parents-in-law live very simply.
She's so lucky.
Many couples develop troubles because
of their bottom drawers.
Some of them even came here
to get a refund.
That's not going to happen to us.
Just show me the best one you got.
I'm jealous. I wish my kids could have
nice parents-in-law like your daughter does.
Look at this one.
- What's all that?
- It's Hae Yoon's bottom drawers.
- I want to see them.
- It's hard to wrap like that.
- What's this?
- It's a dinner set.
- Then what about this?
- Sets of silver spoons and chopsticks.
Is that all?
I have to do the duvet bedding.
I need to know the bed size first.
He still didn't call us. Call him
and tell him to come home soon.
Okay.
- It's Hae Yoon's mom.
- Get it.
Hello.
- Hi, it's me.
- Hi.
I could've asked Hae Yoon to call you but
I did it because we're close enough now.
What did you want to ask me?
What's your bed size?
I'm shopping for the bottom drawers now.
I want to do something practical.
I'm thinking of buying a duvet bedding.
I guess you haven't heard about it yet.
I think you need to talk to her first.
Why do I have to talk to her about your bed size?
They broke up.
Who said that?
Did Jung Hoon say that?
No. Hae Yoon did. She came to look around
her marital home and told us that.
It's so absurd.
Absurd? I think so too...
What the heck? Did she hang up?
- What's going on?
- What happened?
I think this woman caused another problem.
No wonder she said she
would pay for the interior.
Didn't Mrs. Jung know about this?
Don't call her that.
She's just Hae Yoon's mom now.
Don't be so cranky.
She's a parent too. She must
be as shocked as us.
Now, Jung Hoon is the problem.
He had so many difficulties after he broke
up with Hae Yoon last time, right?
He kept drinking.
What makes you so sure about me?
You don't believe I don't love you anymore, do you?
No, I don't.
- How can you not love me?
- Because I fell in love with somebody else.
I can tell you just made that up.
Now I realized why I was attracted
to an orphan and dated one for 5 years.
It was because of the sense of kinship that
comes from having the same background.
Did you change your mind because
I'm the daughter of a rich family?
This is why I didn't tell
you about my background.
I think you have more serious
problems than I do. It's like trauma.
You know what causes that?
The background I'm talking
about is a wound.
A wound from parents.
Do you know? Do you know how it feels
to be rejected by someone you love?
Do you know how scary it is to love
somebody or to be loved by somebody?
I don't know how scary it is to love
somebody or to be loved by somebody.
- What an evil bastard.
- You're an evil bastard.
Just admit it.
I didn't lie to you at least.
But you lied to yourself and to people around you.
Look over my project proposal.
You know what I want to achieve.
I know and that's why I don't
want to give you what you want.
I like that attitude. Do what
you want to do, like this.
Don't try to be innocent
wearing a sheep mask.
You really are confident about me.
You should leave me. It's the best path for you.
- Where are you going?
- Don't be kind. I don't like it.
You're acting perverse.
Let me tell you this again. I don't love you now.
Don't be so mean to your father.
I've been there and done it.
This is why I hate you.
Even if I rejected it
you should've made me get in the car saying,
'you shouldn't be here alone today'.
I'm the problem.
Always.
I lack love and affection.
Min Dong Bi.
You want me to hold you, don't you?
Do you know who I hate the most?
It's you, Gong Ki Joong!
Do you know how much I loved you? If you'd
loved me, my life wouldn't be like this.
- I love you.
- I love Jung Hoon.
He came to my heart. No, he
was already in my heart.
I don't believe that.
Then don't. I don't love
him to make you believe.
Does Hae Yoon know?
- They broke up.
- They did? Because of you?
Do I even have a strong presence to them?
I didn't even have a presence in front of
my ex-boyfriend who I dated for 5 years.
That's not love.
It's a temporary confusion
that a person who was born in a cold place
has when she goes to a warm place.
He was with me whenever I had hard times.
If I go to Jung Hoon's house, there's
this warm atmosphere in his house.
I stay in my house where there's
only cold wind blowing.
But if I go to his house, I feel happy.
Feeling comfortable and warm isn't love?
It is love.
Then it's right that I love him.
That love was what I had for you.
You weren't next to me even once
when I wanted you.
How do you want me to cut your hair?
Just cut it short please.
Will you marry me?
Let's get married quickly.
She's not answering my phone.
What's going on?
She didn't break up with him for sure, right?
What if she did?
Everybody knows that she's getting married.
All she had to do was print the invitation.
It's not a big deal. They'll
forget about it eventually.
So many people get a divorce.
She didn't have the wedding yet.
Hae Jin is one of the many people. Why
are things like this happening to our family?
Don't we have to exorcise or something?
You must be kidding. Many things can happen.
She will endure it.
- She can do it.
- I really respect you, sis.
How could you live after your husband died?
If someone I love died, I would follow him.
Call Hae Jin and ask her if she wants
me to come with her to the court.
You can worry about that in this situation?
You will see if you have a kid.
I said you didn't have to come.
- Are you sure you don't want me to follow you?
- I'm fine.
- Where's Do Hyun?
- He comes home late.
It's so weird. Why did he come back?
He wants a divorce.
I think he thinks staying home
is more favorable to him.
Do you want me to make him leave?
If I stay here, he will leave.
Can you do that? You're busy
preparing for Hae Yoon's wedding.
I came to talk about her with you. I've been
calling her but she's not answering.
Call her. I know you're having hard times
but it's good to distract yourself from it.
- Then you can forget about it for a while.
- Okay.
What happened to her anyway?
I found out when I talked to Mrs. Ha on
the phone. She said they broke up.
Why? Did his family find
out I'm getting a divorce?
No. Her marriage has nothing
to do with your divorce.
Don't feel small because of things like that.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
I should've lived happily.
I'm not worthy of seeing you.
I feel sorry because I think
you had this marriage because of me.
He's a very educated man but
why is he such a douche bag.
I thought an educated man would be
so nice to a woman but he's worse.
My mind keeps changing 12 times in a day.
I feel like I can win this but
then I feel like I'm going to die.
That's how people live a life.
I've been through that too.
Luckily you have me.
I was left in the world with my two little
babies and young sister. I was 38 years old.
I know.
How could you endure all these days?
You can do it if you have to.
Do you eat meals everyday? You shouldn't
skip meals no matter what happens.
I still remember the look on Hae Yoon's face.
How could she say that in front of us?
She said she didn't want to lie to us.
She's honest and has a lot of pride.
I'm wondering why they broke up.
I think it's Dong Bi. Jung Hoon
said it's not but I think it is.
Hae Yoon didn't let it go.
They had a lovers' quarrel.
If that's the case, they can
get back together, right?
- Then we should be careful.
- What?
I know Hae Yoon will be a
good wife to Jung Hoon.
But look at her family. I can't let him suffer
because of her mother. I'm glad they broke up.
Don't do that. How did your
parents treat me at first?
We were very hurt because of that.
It's a different situation.
My parents had some problems emotionally.
Then do you have a problem emotionally, just like them?
You know your own mind, that's why I wanted
to marry you and we still love each other.
- I'm special.
- So is Hae Yoon.
Everyone thinks they're special.
Don't put me and Hae Yoon in the same shoes.
Even if my parents had some problems,
they weren't like Hae Yoon's mom.
You think that because they are your parents.
You probably don't know.
I'm getting mad. What was
wrong with my mom and dad?
You see? You're getting mad because
I'm talking about your parents.
We both weren't free from our parents before.
Let's not talk about other families like that.
I hate when you talk like that.
It's about our son.
Let's not be a teacher for our son's problem.
Thank you.
Why aren't you answering Mom's call?
She's worried. Call her.
It's Hae Yoon.
- Where are you?
- I have a meeting at Gangnam.
Is it true you broke up with Jung Hoon?
- Yeah.
- Is it true?
So are you crying alone somewhere?
No. I'm not going to get drunk and cry by myself.
Don't worry.
Tell her to come here.
She said she has a meeting.
- Go home early though.
- Okay.
You're going to the court, right? Fighting.
Okay.
Fighting to you too.
- Fighting for what?
- For the court tomorrow.
She sounded okay.
She's like the same.
- Then it's serious.
- Why?
Don't you know her? If she cries or
something, that's the start, not the end.
If she really wants to end,
then she does it so quietly.
You went to the salon? You don't
have to try to look nice for me.
You're so funny.
How did you get this?
That's what I want to ask you.
Why did you still have this?
I don't know. Would you like to drink after?
I know many good places.
No. I want to go home early.
I came here to give you that.
Hae Yoon, the best way to forget
about a man is by another man.
After the disengagement, I met so many women.
You don't have to find another man
somewhere else. You met your first love.
I don't want to see another man.
You said you won't date a man after
we broke up. But you met Jung Hoon.
After I broke up with you, I met many guys.
- Hey.
- Bye.
Is she playing hard to get?
I like that.
Hae Yoon.
Hi, Mom.
What are you doing?
There weren't any side dishes so
I made some stir-fried-potato.
You got drunk the other day because of the breakup?
It's all over. I'm not going to drink.
- You don't want to talk about it?
- No, I don't.
I need to know the reason though. You
convinced me so you can marry him.
There wasn't an answer to the marriage. I
can't marry a man when I can't find an answer.
There isn't an answer to your life.
Did Mrs. Ha say something
about the marital house?
No, she didn't say anything.
It's about me and Jung Hoon.
Who broke up first? It was him again?
- No. I did.
- You said you love him.
You said you love him. Why did you break up?
Do you think you're the only one
going through hard times?
Every couple has to go through them
while preparing the wedding.
What you said about love was right.
Love was no big deal.
Reality is much stronger than love.
Did you just realize that?
I bought the bottom drawers
for your parents-in-law today.
What should I do with those now? Huh?
- Go return them.
- How? They were for bottom drawers.
Then we can use them.
I'll pay you back.
Money isn't important in this situation.
Didn't Jung Hoon stop you?
He accepted what I said.
What a nice man.
He listens to people very well. He
listens to me, his mother, and you.
- He's spineless.
- He did the best he could.
Whatever. I'm not going to say
anything about that anymore.
I knew Sang Jin has a crush on you but I
ignored it because I liked Jung Hoon.
I'm glad you broke up with him.
Marry Sang Jin.
- No.
- Why not?
He's not spineless.
He's smart and likes you.
You lied that he's married because you're
worried I'm going to hook you up with him.
I dated him but he cheated on me.
Do you want to live like my sister?
Why do you talk about Hae Jin here?
What's wrong with Hae Jin?
You will be happier to live
with him instead of Jung Hoon.
What should I eat to make me think like you?
You eat the same things that I eat.
Don't be silly.
Do you think he's going to make
the same mistake he did before?
Just date him.
He ruined a family once,
he could do it again. Who said that?
I did. Words can have different
meanings in different situations.
You don't know that?
- Do you want to eat?
- You eat.
I'm going to pack my stuff and
stay at Hae Jin's for a while.
What are you doing?
I was waiting for you.
Let's go drink.
Okay. I'm in the mood
for drinking tonight.
Dad.
- Hi.
- I knew you'd be here.
- What made you come here?
- I'd like to drink with my son.
I'm okay.
Even if you're okay, it's
good to drink on such a day.
It'd be the best if you drink with me.
- Did something happen?
- I'm not getting married.
- You can come with us.
- It's okay.
Come with us. You said you
want to drink tonight.
- It's okay.
- Come on. Let's go.
I'm okay. You came here because you
were worried his feelings got hurt.
I don't want to interrupt
father and son time.
- Then let's drink all together next time.
- Sure.
Let's go.
Father.
I looked over the project proposal again.
Wasn't I supposed to get your invested money by now?
I think the net profit will be lower than the investment.
Bring me a new project.
I know you'd prefer a low cost
strategy to make a bigger profit.
You can't be so cheap about whip-out.
Just bring me a new project.
Can't you just trust your own kid?
Let's drink.
Would you tell me what I'm
wondering about before I ask?
She said she's breaking up with me
because she loves me. I couldn't stop her.
Because I was worried about the same thing.
The reason you two broke up was
because you love each other?
It was a sense of inferiority.
Sense of inferiority?
What inferiority?
I understand Hae Yoon, but what kind
of sense of inferiority do you have?
It's so weird. I feel so small in front of her.
I feel like I have to be a better
man and that I have to be more.
I just feel like I should have more of something.
But the reality is I'm just a salary
man who can't even make 30K in a year.
I guess Hae Yoon also felt
small in front of you.
Since when did your value become money?
What?
If you can make 100K in a year,
do you think you won't feel small?
I thought you had the right values.
I'm sad that you lost your values by facing
reality while preparing the wedding.
- I'm sorry.
- You don't have to feel sorry for me.
I wish you can be stronger and grow
up as you go through these times.
It's okay to let go of yourself by
drinking after you broke up with her.
But if you want to do it, please use me.
Can you promise me that?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I miss you, Ha Jung Hoon.
I guess Hae Yoon also felt small in front of you.
Our love lost to reality.
Our love makes us weaker not stronger.
I think love is forever. It's people who change, not love.
Welcome home. Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
What's wrong with coming
to my daughter's house?
Did you have dinner?
I'll make you dinner.
You said I'm one of the
reasons for the divorce.
I'll be nice to you from now on.
Where are you going? I said I'd make you dinner.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going to sleep here with Mom.
- She's going to stay here with me for a while.
- For a while?
Are you trying to screw me over?
If that's how you feel,
then it's a great success.
- Did you change it?
- Yeah.
Are you going to sleep here with us?
No, I'm not.
- Why?
- You should've seen the look on his face.
He freaked out when he saw me.
- Thank you, Mom.
- For what?
For being my mother.
Where's the ramen?
It's too late to eat that.
- There's nothing to eat.
- Do you want me to make dinner?
Never mind. You should be able
to make your dinner yourself.
This is a bean sprout. This is bracken and this is...
It's okay. I don't need your help.
I'll do it myself. You can go.
Okay then.
Why did she come here?
She came to her daughter's house.
There should be a reason for that?
- I feel uncomfortable. Tell her to leave.
- No.
Tae Hyun likes her and she
might watch him after
we get a divorce. He needs to get used to it.
You think you're going to raise him?
- Not going to happen.
- He's 7.
He needs his mom more than his father.
If we go see a family fact-finding officer, you
will see the officer will think the same.
Don't think this common
opinion would work for you.
There is always an exception.
Your occupation?
- I'm a doctor.
- I'm a housewife.
Educational background?
- PHD.
- High school graduate.
How many times have you married?
This is the second marriage. I met her during
the first marriage so I got a divorce.
This is my first marriage.
So you ruined the marriage.
A plaintiff, Nam Do Hyun, are
you sure you want a divorce?
Yes.
What claim do you make?
I want to claim the
custody and parental rights.
So I can live with my son
as soon as possible.
You both didn't agree on
division of property, right?
What she wants is too much.
She wants half of my hospital grounds
that I bought in Namyangju.
It's like highway robbery.
She has lived a comfortable life during
the marriage even if she had nothing.
A comfortable life? I didn't waste the
money you gave me for living expenses.
And I worked like a servant.
Have you even moved your finger at home?
I gave you 10 million won for living expenses.
You lived a comfortable life with that.
You had much more money than when you
worked as a nurse before we got married.
Did I use all of that money?
I used it for housing.
Who bought that suit you are wearing now?
So he gave you more than
100 million in a year.
I think you did live a comfortable life.
Mrs. Jung Hae Jin, how much money
did you make when you were a nurse?
Just like that, she doesn't know her place.
Ta-da
Did you make them?
I bought it from Ki Joong's restaurant.
- Thank you.
- We should go together for this.
Wedding invitation for Gong
Ki Joong and Han Chae Young.
If I think of Dong Bi, I don't
want to bless him. I'm not going.
- Do you want to break up with me?
- I'll go.
Why are you threatening me?
Do you know how happy I am when you say
you don't want to break up with me?
You're so weird. Why do
you feel happy from that?
My heart drops when you say that.
You fall in love with me. You do.
I think it's time to do it.
Do what?
There's only one thing left between us.
You can't come to my house at night
because of your sister, right?
It's okay. She's staying at her
daughter's house for a while.
Hae Yoon is not getting married
and Hae Jin is getting a divorce.
So she doesn't have time to take care of me.
She told me to sell the
bike but she never checks.
I don't know why Do Hyun has to
do the lawsuit for the divorce.
I think he still has feelings for her.
If he doesn't love her, he would want to finish
it as soon as possible
even if it takes money.
Let's eat.
Here.
The accused, Jung Hae Jin, are
you sure about the divorce?
Yes.
What claim do you make?
I want custody and
parental rights for my child.
And the rate of division of property
should be more than what he requests.
You're a housewife.
After he married me, his sales
for the hospital got tripled.
I assisted him so he can focus on his work.
If I make that much money, you should do that.
You admitted that I was perfect as a wife.
I don't remember.
Oh my god.
How could you do that?
How could you do this to me?
Lower your voice. I think
you're getting very emotional.
This is why I can't communicate with her.
Can we finish this today?
The questions that I asked
you were very simple today.
But next time, it will be more specific.
I'll find out the reason for the divorce.
I think the officer wasn't very
favorable to you.
I know. I'm not stupid.
Now do you see the reality? Without
me, you're just a regular woman.
Even if I give you what you want, you
don't have abilities to protect them.
Let's just finish this. I'll give you some money.
If you agree with that now,
I'm willing to give you more.
Why did you come out alone?
Where's my daughter?
- How do I know?
- You went there with her.
She's probably crying somewhere.
She's facing reality.
Tell her to make an agreement
with me now before she gets hurt.
I think it went well for you today.
But don't be so triumphant.
You never know how it's going to go next.
Don't you think you're being cheap?
You sued her because you can't give her
money? She assisted you for 7 years.
You can make money.
You have abilities to make money.
I know you hate me but because of me, you
could live with a woman like her for 7 years.
She's very nice.
Just give her what she wants
and be friends with each other.
You don't know what's going to happen.
Who knows? You might live with her again.
That's never going to happen.
You should never use the word 'never'.
Did you cry?
Why did you come? I told you not to.
It's the first investigation. I wanted to come.
He looked happy but what's wrong with you?
What happened there?
Mom.
Something's weird.
Why?
According to what the officer said,
after she heard that Do Hyun finished
the first marriage because of Hae Jin,
her attitude towards Hae Jin has changed.
I think you're right.
A married woman is sensitive
about her husband's affair.
Because it doesn't sound
like other people's business.
I'll dig up some information about her.
You didn't tell her that you're getting a
divorce because Do Hyun cheated on you?
She's going to ask about that next time.
Other people get their
divorce done very easily.
It's so important for people to
get married with the right person.
Then what should we do next?
We should get her favor next time.
Don't be so sad.
A person who smiles at
the end is the real winner.
You're right.
When can I go to your house for dinner?
About that.
Hae Yoon must be having a hard
time because of the break up.
Let's finish this first. I'm too
busy to think about other stuff now.
- Let's go.
- Mrs. Jung.
I've saved more money than you think.
Yeah, I know.
I think he likes Hae Yoon.
- I think so.
- You wanted him as her husband.
But he's not really good looking.
I don't like his voice. I'd forgive
his face if he had 1000 million won.
Mom.
Now you're smiling. You feel better now?
Don't make a sad face. You
still have a long way to go.
How can people who have
no mom live in this world?
Is this better or is that one better?
- They look all the same.
- Dude, it's different.
This one looks better.
- I like this one better though.
- Then go with that one.
Hey, can't you be serious?
- I'm so lazy.
- I was with you when you needed me.
So was I. Don't take the credit yourself.
- Do you want to drink?
- No.
I'm not going to drink and ruin myself
just because of a break up with a woman.
That sounds so mature!
Hey.
Why? Did it hurt you?
No.
You said you watched a video about the
beautiful wedding, right? Show me that.
- I couldn't find it.
- It's on my computer.
I need to watch that and there
isn't any food at my house.
- So what?
- I don't know. What do you want to do?
- His wedding is soon.
- Yeah.
His wedding is going at full speed.
Whatever. I don't care.
Don't pretend to be okay. Just
tell me if you are hurting.
Mr. Ha.
Were you surprised that I called?
- No.
- I wanted to hang out with you.
Now I can do it.
What do you like to eat?
Let's eat what you want.
Okay.
- Hi, Mrs. Ha.
- Hi. Long time no see.
- I've wanted to eat your food.
- Sure. Come eat.
What's wrong with her? Is she mad at me?
No.
Go to my room.
- Are you mad at something?
- Don't be close with Dong Bi.
Mom.
I know you're not getting married to
Hae Yoon but I keep faith with her.
Dong Bi hurt Hae Yoon's feeling.
I said it's not that.
Anyway, a man and a woman
can't be friends.
Where's the mom that I like? The mom that
understands me and listens to me.
- I'm doing this for you.
- If it's for me, then just do nothing.
Do you think I'm all better?
Why do you talk about Hae Yoon?
I got dumped by a woman
because I'm incompetent.
Why is it because you're incompetent?
What would Dad do if he were me?
If it was him, would he have let you go?
I heard everything.
Sorry. My mom is sensitive lately.
I'm going to go.
- Are you holding ancestral rites now?
- I told you I'm not going to drink.
I met with Hae Yoon. I tried to make her
feel better but she was so mad already.
Seeing things is stronger
than hearing things.
So she wouldn't believe me even
if I tell her everything.
You should tell her until she believes you.
You're the only friend to her.
I'm not her supporting actress anymore.
If you're a supporting actress, does that
mean Ki Joong is my supporting actor?
He can't be a supporting actor.
He has a great background and he
has this loneliness on his face.
That's what a woman really likes.
That guy loved you. You're
a very attractive woman.
Be confident.
You're stupid. A woman changes
her mind very easily.
The confidence that you get from someone
you love is like a sand castle.
Let's drink just one shot, friend.
Okay. Just this one.
- What do you think?
- It's delicious.
You could've went to a
nicer restaurant than this.
I wanted to come to a place like this with you.
It's very warm and friendly.
When I was young I was jealous of kids
who ate food here with their dads.
I see.
Let's eat.
Bring us more pickled radish.
Let's have dessert at a place that I want to go.
Sure.
- What do you think?
- It's delicious.
I come here often with my wife.
I also liked the restaurant
where we had dinner tonight.
Thank you.
Hae Yoon.
I was so happy to think that
you will become a part of our family.
I'm not good enough to be
your daughter-in-law.
After all these years,
I realized the most important thing for a
marriage is how much they love each other.
But I don't think so.
People spend money to feel happy.
But if you're with someone you love, happiness
comes to you even if you don't pay for it.
It's free.
I know there isn't anything that's free in the world.
But love is free.
Living a life is a series of conflicts.
You can't just solve them as
if you are solving a math problem.
Thank you.
Next time, you should call me first.
Don't be nice to me. I can't leave you.
If you can't leave, then don't.
Choi Mo Lyung famously said
that to Kim Ji Mi in the 70s.
Do you know Choi Mo Lyung?
He's the father of Choi Min Su.
You know him.
You're not that young anymore.
I know.
Do you live in the 1970s
or in the year of 2012?
Mrs. Jung.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
- I hung out with Hae Yoon tonight.
- I see.
I went out to buy some snacks and drinks.
You are having a get-together with your daughters.
Yeah, it's a get-together with my daughters.
You achieved my wife's dream.
Her dream is to hang out with
her daughter if there is one.
Why is that her dream? She can just have one.
- It's kind of hard to have a daughter.
- I know.
- It's cold.
- Yeah.
- It's cold. You should go.
- Yeah, Mrs. Jung.
- It was nice seeing you.
- It was nice seeing you too.
What's going on?
Why did you come here with him?
- You said you're done with Jung Hoon.
- Mom, ask me one by one.
You need to get used to a new life.
Cross the line.
He came to my school.
He's a great man. If my dad was
alive, I think he'd be like Mr. Ha.
He was very innocent.
Hae Jin got that from him.
But you aren't because you're more like me.
- I like Mr. Jung.
- Did you guys get back together?
I'm done with him. I think he came to say bye.
I could've been a part of his family, you know.
That's useless. If he came to convince
you, he should've acted more clearly.
It's like he has no guts.
- Can I sleep in her house too?
- Yeah. It's far to go home now.
- How did the court thing go?
- Failed.
I can hear everything.
- You should come and dance with me.
- After this shot.
Me too.
What the heck?
You haven't changed a bit.
Who is this woman?
- Why did you hit him?
- Who is she?
- You have bad taste.
- What are you doing here?
I came to dance.
I'm dating this man.
You look so old now.
You should get plastic surgery
if you want more customers.
You still make biting remarks.
- I heard you're getting a divorce.
- How did you know?
- I met Hae Jin.
- Why?
Did she ask you for something?
The best thing I've done in my life
was getting a divorce with you.
You're so cheap. Just give her what you want.
You're too skinny. If you lose weight like
this, you'll suffer from osteoporosis later.
What was that? No wonder
why you cheated on her.
What was the good evidence that
you were talking about last time?
Why did you marry women like them?
Hae Jin smashed my apartment and
that woman just smashed you.
- I don't understand.
- Let's get out.
He said he's going to give me money if I give up my child.
That's why I'm getting a divorce.
Every man for his own.
If you don't like it, I'd just
suck it up and live with him.
- I did a good job, didn't I?
- Good job.
I feel so bad for you. The women
you got married to are so weird.
They're so big and ugly.
I'm tall but I have skinny bones.
Go to sleep.
Sleep here.
I'd like to but I'm at war.
If I don't come back home,
my mother-in-law will think she won.
I guess there's a heater
in this bathroom.
Yeah, isn't it warm?
It's so nice.
I tried so hard to make
you live well and warm.
Mom, let's not talk about
that tonight and have fun.
Okay, let's have fun.
This is so nice.
Are we all going to sleep here?
It's big enough.
I feel empty without Aunt Deul Rae.
I should've told her to come.
She must feel lonely.
No, this isn't good.
No. I can't sleep with him.
- Hey, sis.
- Do you want to come to Hae Jin's house?
We are all here.
We feel empty without you.
I'm fine.
I'm kind of tired.
- Don't forget to lock the door.
- Okay.
Hi.
It's Min Deul Rae.
It's your name.
Didn't know you can be like this. You
got cheesy after you started dating me.
So you don't like it?
- I like it.
- Do you hate flowers?
I like it. I like Min Deul Rae.
I like everything you give me.
I like you when you do that.
You don't play hard to get.
You like everything about me.
It's kind of cold here.
Can you turn on the heater?
The gas bill is expensive.
My sister is going to freak out.
Alright.
Then let's increase the
temperature by our temperature.
- I can't sleep with you tonight.
- Why?
You don't have to know.
- What is it?
- I'm going to lose weight.
I can't show this body.
It's the same in the dark.
No. Let's just talk tonight while in this mood.
What is it like talking in this mood?
We can start doing it by filling the glass.
Cheers.
It feels so good to do a pace book,
after such a long time.
Your skin looks so good and pale.
I should've gotten her skin.
I got her skin so mine is pale too.
You should be thanking me
because you got my skin.
Skin is very important to women.
She's so skinny just like you.
I'm just like my dad. I'm big.
Because of your dad, your
arms and legs are long.
- That's your charm.
- So cheesy.
- But I don't like your make up.
- Look at her. She's trying to teach me again.
No, I'm not. Mom, natural-looking
make up is the trend these days.
Who does their make up like you these days?
You think this make up looks good on anybody?
If you do it wrong, you
look so old-fashioned.
But I look like an actress. People
say I look like Lee Mi Suk.
Sis, she's so funny.
- Why so funny?
- Because you don't make any sense.
- Hey!
- When are we going to drink?
Alright.
All three of us haven't got together in so long.
Let's start our bright new days from tomorrow.
Here's a shot for my oldest daughter.
Wake up, Gong Ki Joong. I know you woke up
because you're sensitive when you sleep.
- I need to talk to you.
- About what?
About business.
I hate to talk about business
right after I get up.
Let's go to the living room.
You.
I'm going to throw you to the wind.
Who were you with? You didn't
even tell me who you were with.
- I was with Hae Yoon.
- Honey, are you serious?
Their break up is a very
good chance for Jung Hoon.
Besides, she broke up with Jung Hoon first.
Hae Yoon is a nice woman. She
was about to become part of our family.
Please. Don't make things worse!
Do you remember this, Mom?
After Dad passed away, you were in a
partnership with your friend, but she tricked you.
She couldn't help it. She needed money desperately
so she had to run away with my money.
Money made her do that.
She was very nice before.
Anyway, when you were so busy finding her...
I remember that.
When I cried because I missed Mom, she
made me food and carried me on her back.
After I put you to sleep, I went
to Mom's room and cried.
I was so scared. I felt like
I was the only one in the world.
You should've woke me up.
You were still young.
But I'm your older sister.
Mom said I should take good care
of you because I'm the older sister.
It's all because of your dad.
What was I supposed to do after he passed away?
I was a housewife before.
He should've left me with a lot
of money before he died.
But Mom, I feel the same thing.
I'm alone in this house.
That evil bastard.
That time was better than now. Because I
knew it would end when you came back home.
Do you not see me here?
- I'm home.
- Come here.
- You guys have fun.
- You bastard, what have you done to her?
I think you're drunk. Go to sleep.
I am drunk but I don't have to go to sleep.
- Just leave him alone.
- Yeah.
Mrs. Jung, you should step back
for your daughters' happiness.
You have that kind of temper
that doesn't help them at all.
You son of a bitch, don't
talk to my mom like that.